export const askedQuestions = [
    {
      question: "What is Proactic?",
      answer:
        "Proactic is a social media marketing automation tool designed to help businesses streamline their social media efforts.",
    },
    {
      question: "How does Proactic work?",
      answer:
        "Proactic automates the process of scheduling, posting, and analyzing social media content across multiple platforms.",
    },
    {
      question: "Which social media platforms does Proactic support?",
      answer:
        "Proactic supports popular social media platforms such as Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, LinkedIn, and more.",
    },
    {
      question: "Can I schedule posts in advance with Proactic?",
      answer:
        "Yes, Proactic allows you to schedule posts in advance, ensuring your content is published at the optimal times.",
    },
    {
      question: "Does Proactic provide analytics?",
      answer:
        "Proactic offers detailed analytics to help you track the performance of your social media campaigns and make data-driven decisions.",
    },
    {
      question: "Is Proactic suitable for small businesses?",
      answer:
        "Yes, Proactic is designed to be user-friendly and scalable, making it suitable for businesses of all sizes.",
    },
    {
      question: "What is Proactic?",
      answer:
        "Proactic is a social media marketing automation tool designed to help businesses streamline their social media efforts.",
    },
    {
      question: "What is Proactic?",
      answer:
        "Proactic is a social media marketing automation tool designed to help businesses streamline their social media efforts.",
    },
    {
      question: "What is Proactic?",
      answer:
        "Proactic is a social media marketing automation tool designed to help businesses streamline their social media efforts.",
    },
    {
      question: "What is Proactic?",
      answer:
        "Proactic is a social media marketing automation tool designed to help businesses streamline their social media efforts.",
    },
  ];
  